Murder.
Mystery.
The macabre.
What is it about a heart-boiled
detective femme fertile,
and the cold steel of a gun,
keeps our bedside lamps burning
into the wee hours of the morning.
However the spell is cast,
tonight we honor a master of the form
and celebrate the launch
of storm fall.
Call me when you're ready
to wash that off.
The stunning conclusion to his best selling
derek storm mystery series.
Ladies and gentlemen
The master of the macabre,
Rick Castle.
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:FRM@´ó±¦
Sync:FRS@°²ÄÈ¸â
Who are you?
Alison tisdale--
24, grad student at n.Y.U.,
Part of the social work program.
Nice place for a social worker.
Daddy's money.
Neighbors called to complain about the muc.
When she didn't answer,
they had the super check on her.
No signs of struggle.
He knew her.
Even bought her flowers.
Who says romance is dead?
I do, every saturday night.
A little lipstick wouldn't hurt.
I'm just saying.
So what'd he give her besides roses?
Two shots to the chest,
Small caliber.
Does this look familiar to anyone?
No, but i'm not the one with
a thing for freaky ones.
Just give me a "jack shot jill over bill"
So i can get my collar and go home.
Oh, but the freaky ones require more.
They reveal more.
Look at how he left her, covered modestly.
So?
So despite all of the effort,
all of the preparation,
You won't find any evidence of sexual abuse.
You really get that from just this?
This, plus, i've seen this before.
You've seen it before? Where?
Roses on her body, sunflowers on her eyes?
Don't you guys read?
What kind of idiot
Kills off his best-Selling main character?
Are you asking as my bloodsucking publisher
Or as my bloodsucking ex-Wife?
Oh, is that what you're doing?
Punishg me by killing the golden goose?
Oh, come on. I may be petty and shortsighted,
But i'm not that petty and shortsighted.
Really? Then why?
Writing derrick used to be fun.
Now it's like work.
Mm. God forbid you should work.
I mean, you could have retired him,
You could have crippled him.
You could have had him join the friggin' circus.
But, no, you had to put a bullet through his head.
Yeah, real messy, too. Big exit wound.
Don't worry. Derrick storm is not
the golden goose here. I am.
I wrote half a dozen best
sellers before him.
What makes you think i'm gonna stop now?
Oh, i don't know.
The fact the new book was due nine weeks ago?
You can't rush genius.
Genius, richard? Try blockage.
I heard you haven't written in months.
That's ridiculous.
My sources are very reliable.
Well, they're wrong.
They better be.
If i don't have a new muscript
On my desk in the next three weeks,
Black pawn is prepared to demand
the return of your advance.
You wouldn't dare.
Try me. Just try me.
You know, i already returned that advance.
I spent it divorcing you.
Really, dollface,
who does homework at a party?
I have a test next week.
So do i--Liver function.
You don't see me studying.
All right, give me a hit of the bubbly.
Make that two.
Hey, kiddo. Sales must be slipping.
They're only serving the soft stuff.
Hey, dad.
Hey, sweetie. So, mother...
Shh! Shh! Shh! Not so loud.
I'm still hoping to get lucky.
Did you tell gina i was having trouble writing?
Oh, i told her nothing of the sort. I...
I may have said something
About spending your days
moping in your underwear
Waiting for post time at belmont.
But hey, you're an artist.
It's expected.
We had aeal.
I let you live with us,
but you don't talk about my work.
What's to talk about?
You haven't done any
-  since i moved in.
- Gram.
- Well, he hasn't.
- Whatever i have and haven't done,
I would just appreciate it if you wouldn't share it
With my ex-Wife.
Oh, what's the big deal?
Hang on, sweetie.
I just got a hit on my "graydar."
Bingo! No ring. Stand back, ki.
Mama's going fishing.
You should have me committed.
For what, letting her move in?
I think it's sweet.
Won't be when i strangle her.
You know i'm only 15, right?
You're an old soul.
Yeah, well, me and my "soul" can wait.
When i was your age...
I can't tell that story.
It's wildly inappropriate,
which, oddly, is my point.
Don't you want to have
wildly inappropriate stories
That you can't tell your children?
I think you have enough
of those for the both of us.
Life should be an adventure.
You want to know why i killed derrick?
There were no more surprises.
I knew exactly What was going to happen
every moment of every scene.
It's just like these parties.
They've become so predictable.
"I'm your biggest fan.
Where do you get your ideas?"
And the ever popular
"will you sign my 'chest'?"
That one i don't mind so much.
Yeah, well, f.Y.I., i do.
Just once, i'd like someone to come up to me
And say something new.
Mr. Castle?
Where would you like it?
Detective kate beckett, nypd.
We need to ask you a few questions
About a murder that took place earlier tonight.
That's new.
Castle S01e01
Mr. Castle.
You've got quite a rap sheet
for a best-Selling author.
Disorderly conduct,
Uh, resisting arrest?
Boys will be boys.
It says here that you stole a police horse?
Borrowed.
Ah. And you were nude at the time.
It was spring.
And every time, the charges were dropped.
What can i say?
The mayor is a fan.
But if it makes you feel any better,
I'd be happy to let you spank me.
Mr. Castle, this whole "bad boy charm" thing
That you've got going
Might work for bimbettes and celebutantes.
Me? I work for a living,
So that makes you one
of two things in my world--
Either the guy who makes my life easier
Or the guy who makes my life harder.
And trust me, you do not want to be
The guy who makes my life harder.
Okay.
Alison tisdale,
Daughter of real estate mogul jonathan tisdale.
- She's cute.
- She's dead.
Did you ever meet her? Book signing?
Charity event?
It's possible.
She's not in my little black book,
If that's what you're asking.
What about this guy?
Marvin fisk, small claims lawyer.
Most of my claims tend
to be on the, um, large side.
So what's this got to do with me?
Fisk was found murdered
in his office two weeks ago.
I didn't put it together
Until we saw the tisdale crime scene tonight.
"Flowers for your grave."
And this is how we found marvin fisk,
Right out of "hell hath no fury."
Looks like i have a fan.
Yeah, a really deranged fan.
Oh, you don't look deranged to me.
What?
"Hell hath no fury"--
Angry wiccans out for blood.
Come on. Only hard-Core castle
groupies read that one.
Do any of these groupies ever write you letters?
Disturbing letters?
Oh, all my fan mail is disturbing.
It's an occupational hazard.
Because sometimes in cases like this,
We find that the
- killer attempts to--
- Killer attempts to contact the subject of his obsession.
I'm also pretty well-Versed in
psychopathic methodologies.
Another occupational hazard.
And do you know you have gorgeous eyes?
So i take it that you won't have any objection
To us going through your mail?
Knock yourself out.
Can i get copies of those?
Copies?
I have this poker game.
It's mostly other writers--
Patterson, cannell-- You know, best-Sellers.
You have no idea how jealous
those would make them.
- Jealous?
- That i have a copycat.
Oh, my gosh.
In my world, that's the red badge of honor.
That's the criminal cooperstown.
People are dead, mr. Castle.
I'm not asking for the bodies,
just the pictures.
I think we're done here.
* i'm just a gal who cain't say no *
* i'm in a terrible fix *
* i always say, "come on, let's go" *
* just when i ought to-- *
Hey, kiddo!
I'm just showing burt here
how we did it at the palace.
Does he know it's your theme song?
Ready to bring it home, ducky?
Hey! Yes!
Five, six, seven, eight.
* i'm just a fool when lights are low... *
You're missing the late show.
I saw it in previews.
Looks like we got a new lead.
His name is burt. He does magic.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
Let's hope he disappears by morning.
C'est apres minuit dans une school night.
Don't you turn into a pumpkin or something?
Not when your dad's been
escorted away by cops.
How was the slammer?
Anyone make you their bitch?
Sorry, switchblade.
Still belong to you. Baby bird?
- I already brushed.
- Your loss.
So are you gonna tell me about it
Or do i have to look it up on the fan sites?
No, we had a deal.
Surf all the internet you want,
Stay off the fan sites.
Seriously, dad, are
you in some kind of trouble?
Despite my best efforts, no.
They want my help on a case.
A case?
Apparently, someone's been killing people
The way i kill them in my books.
- That's horrible.
- Yeah.
How many?
Two so far.
Are you okay?
Yeah. It's just so senseless.
Murder usually is.
No, murder usually makes
a great deal of sense--
Passion, greed, politics.
What's senseless here
Is the books that the killer chose.
"Hell hath no fury,"
"Flowers for your grave"--
My truly lesser works.
Why would a psychotic fan pick those?
Maybe because he's psychotic.
Come on. It's bedtime.
You can figure it out in the morning.
- What are those?
- Castle's greatest hits.
You're gonna familiarize yourselves
With all of his murder scenes, so we don't miss any.
Got any on tape?
First victim--Male lawyer.
Second victim-- Female social worker.
Somewhere in these books,
those two are connected.
"From the library of katherine beckett."
Do you have a problem with reading, ryan?
Yo, check it, girl. You're totally a fan.
Right, of the genre.
Right, the--The genre.
That's why you're blushing.
What are you, 12?
Profiling indicates a perp with low intelligence,
Someone who has or thinks he has
A personal relationship with our author.
So that's where we start.
What?
I work dead bodies all day.
The last thing i want to do when i go home
Is read murder books.
Aren't you curious?
Curious?
About how people can do these
kinds of things to one another.
Whoever did this read castle's books,
And somewhere in those pages
Is the answer to where he'll strike next.
Okay.
Is all that castle's mail?
His fans love him
Almost as much as he loves himself.
Can you take that back to briefing, please?
Did we hear back from the lab?
Yeah, scene was negative
for d.N.A. And prints,
Just like fisk. The guy's careful.
What about tisdale and fisk, any connection?
Other than your boy there? No.
What's he doing here?
Maybe he likes you.
Detective beckett.
Captain?
Yes, sir?
Mr. Castle's offered to assist
with the investigation.
Really?
It's the least i can do for the city i love.
Considering the nature of the crime scenes,
I think it's a good idea.
Sir, can i talk to you for a minute, in private?
Nope.
What?
Nothing.
No, it's just, uh,
The way your brow furrows
when you're thinking--
It's cute.
I mean, not if you were playing poker.
Then it'd be deadly. But otherwise...
can i ask you a question?
Shoot.
Why are you here?
You don't care about the victims,
So you aren't here for justice.
You don't care that the
guy's aping your books,
So you aren't here 'cause you're outraged.
So what is it, rick?
Are you here to annoy?
I'm here for the story.
The story?
Why those people?
Why those murders?
Sometimes there is no story.
Sometimes the guy is just a psychopath.
There's always a story,
Always a chain of events that
makes everything make sense.
Take you, for example.
Under normal circumstances,
you should not be here.
Most smart, good-Looking women become lawyers, not cops.
And yet, here you are. Why?
I don't know, rick.
You're the novelist. You tell me.
Well, you're not bridge and tunnel.
No trace of the boroughs when you talk,
So that means manhattan, that means money.
You went to college, probably a pretty good one.
You had options.
Yeah, you had lots of options--
Better options, more socially acceptable options--
And you still chose this.
That tells me something happened.
Not to you.
No, you're wounded, but you're not that wounded.
No, it was somebody you cared about.
It was someone you loved.
And you probably could've lived with that,
But the person responsible was never caught.
And that, detective beckett, is why you're here.
Cute trick.
But don't think you know me.
The point is, there's always a story.
You--You just have to find it.
I think i just did.
Lab's got lifts off the letter.
Whose?
The system's backlogged.
It'll take a week to run a match.
A week?
Welcome to reality, superstar.
Well, never did much like reality.
Mayor's office.
Hi, denise. It's rick castle.
- Hi.
- Yeah, is he in?
- Hold on.
- Thanks.
Like i said, the mayor's a fan.
Rick!
Yo, big cheese. It's ricky.
- You doing okay?
- Yeah, of course.
- What's up?
- Well, i don't know where you went.
We looked all over for you. You took off with that girl.
The man's got the mayor on speed dial.
The rich really are different.
You want himhe's yours.
A control freak like you with
something you can't control?
No, no. That's gonna be more
fun than shark week.
Okay, you will have your prints in an hour.
Mr. Castle?
Half of the guys here are waiting for prints.
You don't just jump the line.
Oh, i think somebody feels threatened.
- I am not threatened.
- No, no, i get it.
I can call the mayor, and you can't.
We have procedure, protocol.
Yeah, and you always come to
a complete stop at a red light
And you never fudge your taxes.
Tell me something. Do you ever have any fun?
You know, let your hair down? Drop your top?
A little "cops gone wild"?
You do know i'm wearing a gun?
Beckett, midtown. They just found another one.
"Death of a prom queen."
Maintenance found her an hour ago.
Kendra pitney. She lives in the building.
All right. Let's get her out of the water.
Um, you just stay here and don't touch anything.
Hi, i'm richard castle. I'm consulting.
Richard castle the author?
On my better days.
Lanie parish, medical examiner. I love your books.
You know, you have a real gift with the details of death.
I thought i told you to stay over there.
I got lonely.
You got a c.O.D.?
Not until the full exam. But this wasn't a stabbing.
Lack of blood around the wound
Suggests she was dead before it was inserted.
No foam around the mouth, so we know she didn't drown.
Oh, you're good.
Yeah, yeah. She was killed first and then posed,
Just like the others.
Yeah. I know. Cai have a word?
Something wrong?
This is a homicide investigation,
Not a day at disneyland.
If i give you an order,
i expect you to obey it.
Then you don't know me very well.
You know, in my book, the dress was blue.
Stop trying to change the subject.
Did tisdale and fisk know each other?
We haven't found a connection. Why?
What about motive?
He's a serial killer. He doesn't need motive.
Beckett. Okay.
They got a match off the print.
Kyle cabot--He's in brooklyn. We got him.
- Stay here.
- Scout'shonor.
Kyle cabot! Nypd! Open up!
Kyle cabot! Nypd!
Room clear. Room clear.
All clear.
You should invite him to join your book club.
Beckett! You gotta see this.
Oh, that's creepy.
I was never a scout.
Hey, beckett.
Alison's blouse.
I'm guessing he kept trophies.
.22 caliber.
Show me your hands!
Hands in the air!
Let us see your hands, cabot!
Let me see your hands!
He's still not speaking.
State medical records indicate
He's got pervasive developmental disorder.
Well, that explains his fixation with me.
P.D.D. Sometimes manifests
In an obsession with a single subject.
Yeah, well, your superfan also has a history of delusions.
Guess who his caseworker was.
Alison tisdale.
Yeah.
Her files indicate that he was on pretty
heavy antipsychotics.
Limited telligence,
Thinks he has a personal relationship with his hero--
Looks like your profile was right, detective beckett.
So... what, that--That's it?
What more do you want? Evidence is in his apartment,
We can connect him with the three victims--
Two from the diner where he worked,
And tisdale was his social worker.
Call the d.A. Get him a legal aid.
- Okay.
- I'm--That's, uh, it's too easy.
The reader would never buy it.
This isn't one of your books, castle.
Out here, we find a gustanding over a body with a gun,
He's usually the guy who did it.
You know this kid was in and out of the system for years?
Doesn't seem like he ever got the proper treatment
Until alison tisdale took over his case file.
She's the one who got him a job at the diner,
And her notes seem to say heas doing okay.
Well, you can let the d.A. Worry about all that now.
Our job is done.
Yeah.
Hey, um, can you leave the box? I'll take care of it tomorrow.
Castle, i'm kinda glad that you killed off storm.
Less competition.
Mm.
That's $20 to you, cannell.
You're bluffin', patterson.
Cough up some of that tv money and you'll find out.
Ah, bet's to you, ricky.
Castle?
- Castle!
- Hmm?
- Bet's to you.
- Oh. Sorry.
I know that look-- Story trouble.
Yeah, you never should've killed off storm.
That was a big mistake. I w-- I would've retired him.
Or crippled him. I mean, the man was money.
You don't see me Puttin' a bullet through alex cross' head.
Yeah, my boy shane scully's gonna be fueling my private jet
Long after people have all forgotten about storm.
Oh, you know what? Just for that, i am gonna call.
So what's the problem, ricky?
Maybe we can help.
I'm working on this thing. It starts with a famous author.
Some psycho starts staging murders
Like the way he does in his books.
That's pretty self-Aggrandizing, isn't it?
This is castle we're talking about.
So... The crime scenes are clean.
Doesn't leave any fingerprints. Doesn't leave any d.N.A.
But the psycho writes the author a fan letter
With his prints all over it.
Well, that leads the cops to his apartment,
Where they find enough evidence to convict him.
And then?
- That's it.
- That's it?
Yeah. They arrest him.
That's terrible. No wonder you're blocked.
And here's another thing--
The guy doesn't leave his prints at the scene of the crime,
But he sends a letter with his prints on it?
Ahya lost me there.
- And what about a twist?
- Yeah. Where's the twist?
Yeah, right. Like, uh... like,
maybe somebody set this kid up.
That's what your story needs--
The character who thinks the kid's innocent,
Keeps digging until he finds the truth.
Oh, i have just the guy.
What are you doing?
It's a novelist's habit--
Poking through other people's mail,
Checking their medicine cabinets.
Why are you still here?
I just came by to give you this.
It's a little something to...
Memorialize our brief partnership.
Don't look so suspicious.
Go on. Open it.
I got you an advance copy.
I even signed it to you.
Not that you're a fan.
Thanks. That's actually kind of...
Sweet.
- Well...
It was nice to have met you, detective beckett.
He didn't.
Oh! He did!
Richard castle, you are under arrest
For felony theft and obstruction of justice.
You forgot making you look bad.
You know, for a minute there,
You actually made me believe that you were human.
Cuff him.
Ooh! Bondage. My safe word is "apples."
Oh, there's no nd to be gentle.
How'd you find me anyway?
I'm a detective. That's what i do.
My mother told you, didn't she?
By the way, the rose petals in the tisdale murder?
They're grandiflora, not hybrid teas.
I'll make a note of it.
Yeah, you probably should
Since it means kyle cabot is innocent.
Thank you, officer.
- Hello, father.
- Hello, daughter.
I wish i could say i was surprised.
It's my fault, really. He never had a father figure.
Oh, that's not true, mother. I had lots of father figures.
I see you've met captain montgomery
And detective beckett.
And they have agreed to drop the charges
If you agree to behave.
No more interference with this case, mr. Castle.
Do we understand each other?
Yeah.
But you still got the wrong guy.
I... really.
Darling, must you always
Have to make a comment?
Nah. No, no, no.
Don't tell me that he got to you.
Please. He didn't get to me.
She did.
Who--Alison?
Marvin fisk, first murder. Kyle knew him from the diner.
And then he kills alison, his social worker.
And then he kills kendra pitney, also from the diner.
So?
So he starts with a murder of convenience
And then escalates to a murder of somebody he knows very well
And then goes back to a murder of convenience?
It doesn't make any sense.
Somebody set up kyle to take the fall.
Somebody who knew enough about his fixation with me
To use it to get away with murder.
That means we're not looking for a serial killer.
We're looking for a good, old-Fashioned murderer--
Someone with motive.
You think the victims were somehow related?
Police would've found it by now.
Now if i were writing the story,
The killer would've only wanted one of the victims dead.
He would've killed the other ones just to cover up the crime.
How do you get away with one murder by committing two more?
At one death, you look for motive.
At two, you look for a connection.
At three, you look for someone like kyle.
At three, you don't need motive,
Because mentally unstable serial killers don't usually have one.
That makes about as much sense as "mousetrap."
I did that play eight times a week for a year.
I still have no idea what it's about.
Castle was right.
If he was trying to follow his boo,
Then the roses on alison's body were wrong,
And fisk should've been suffocated by a plastic bag,
Not strangled with a necktie.
And kendra's dress Should've been blue, not yellow.
For an obsessive, It would've been impossible
not to get the details right.
Well, if it wasn't him, then who was it?
The killer had to have known both his intended victim
And kyle fairly well.
The only victim that had any real knowledge
Of kyle's obsessive condition
Would've been alison tisdale.
Alison's the key.
She's the one that the killer is trying to hide.
Well, as far as we know, she wasn't seeing anyone.
And none of her other case profiles fit the profile.
Well, somebody had to know something about her.
So if the killer found out about kyle through alison,
Then alison must've been the intended target.
Somebody wanted alison dead. We just have to figure out why.
If i have to keep bailing you out,
You're gonna need to raise my allowance...
by a lot.
Mine, too.
Hi, i'm rick castle.
I have an appointment to see mr. Tisdale.
=====
===
Is he now?
This is not what it looks like.
This, uh...
okay, this is exactly what it looks like,
But i can explain.
You coming?
Did alison ever mention
Having enemies or being threatened?
People loved her.
All she wanted was to make the world a better place.
I told all this to the other detective.
I know, sir. We're just following up.
Did alison know anybody who could've profited
From her death?
Mr. Castle, i may be rich, but my daughter was not.
She abhorred money.
What little she had, she gave to charity.
Thank you, sir.
Mr. Tisdale, "fortune" magazine estimated your net worth
At nearly $100 million.
Is that true?
I don't check day to day.
But it's in the ballpark?
I've been lucky, yes.
Appreciate your time.
Wh-What happens to all that money
If something happens to you?
Castle.
Half of my estate goes to my charitable foundation,
And the rest to my children.
I mean, my son.
Thank you.
What was that all about?
He's dying.
Who's dying? Tisdale?
You want a hot dog? I want a hot dog.
What do you take on your-- Aah! Apples, apples, apples!
- What makes you think he's dying?
- Okay!
- You see those pictures in his office?
- Yeah.
He's much thinner now--Like sick thin, not workout thin.
His daughter was just murdered.
And the way he kept touching his hair, like he's self-Conscious.
You think it was a piece?
It's a good one, but it's new to him.
The chemo's relatively recent.
And he was wearing makeup.
He's trying to look healthier than he is.
Doesn't want his shareholders to know.
So he's got cancer. That doesn't mean that he's terminal.
But it's a much better story if he is.
You interview the brother?
There was never a reason to.
Well, now there is.
- You got hot mustard?
- Yeah.
- Harrison tisdale.
Hey, mitch, let's get these pallets on the truck.
Detective kate beckett. Rick castle.
We'd like to ask you some questions about your sister.
Yeah, anything i can do. Uh, let's head inside.
Last time i saw her? About a month ago at dad's.
You know, i... still can't believe she's gone.
Were you close?
Ah, everybody loved her. I mean, my sister--
She just wanted to see the best in people,
Even that kid who killed her.
You know, she did everything she could to help that guy.
Even brought him around here once
To see if i could get him a job.
But you didn't.
I can't afford to, all right?
My employees mess up,
I lose my bond.
I don't know. Maybe if i'd helped him...
Things would be different.
How'd your sister react when yourad told you he was dying?
She was upset.
We both were.
Now that she's dead, your inheritance stands to double.
What are you suggesting? You already caught the killer.
Yeah, we did, but the first thing his lawyers will do
Is shift suspicion to someone else,
someone with motive.
And then they'll stick me on the stand
And ask me why i didn't investigate,
And then the jury will have doubts.
And we don't want them to have doubts, do we?
No.
So you'll have to excuse me for asking,
But where were you the night of your sister's murder?
I was traveling... on business.
Actually, i was out of the country
For all three murders.
Here. Check the stamps on that if it's useful.
A u.S. Passport.
Absolutely unassailable.
I was sure it was him.
Oh, don't take it so hard.
After all, you're just a writer.
What?
Nothing.
Oh, come on.
He's lying.
I mean, i get him knowing where he was
The night of his sister's murder,
But the other two victims?
He didn't pause, he didn't ask for dates,
He didn't even check his calendar,
But he was ready with an alibi.
In my experience, innocent people do not prepare alibis.
So i was right.
Okay, give me the dates and flights.
Why can't you just admit i was right?
Because he totally fooled you. He totally bought the alibi.
I had a fleeting moment of self-Doubt.
So?
His credit card company confirms
He paid for three round-Trip tickets.
Dates coincide with the three murders.
So according to his credit card, tisdale was out of the country.
Wait a minute. So now i'm not right?
Which means the passport stamps were forged.
I'm gonna call passport control and have 'em check their logs.
That's, uh, not how he would've done it.
You got a better idea, ricky?
Second passport.
And how would he get one of those?
Oh, with his money? Trust me.
On the black market, it would be a piece of cake.
So he leaves the country on his own,
Comes back with the other passport, commits murder,
Flies out and then comes back in on his own.
Perfect alibi, perfect murder.
But almost impossible to prove.
Unless you find the second passport.
Gotta be freaked after your little meet and greet.
Keep eyeballs on him. If he moves, i wanna know.
The things that people will do for money.
This guy killed his own sister in cold blood
And two more people to cover it up.
He's either a world-Class sociopath,
Or there's a lot more to this story than just money.
Judge markway, please.
Oh, markway. Tell him i said hello.
No, seriously. They're redoing the entire back nine.
Oh, man, i loved that course. When are they gonna reopen it?
Judge, i hate to break up "golf digest,"
But i have an exigent situation here.
Very well, detective. Play through.
We need a search warrant.
She needs a search warrant.
For the home and office of harrison tisdale.
Harrison tisdale? As in jonathan tisdale's son?
-  Yes.
- Yep. He murdered his sister
And killed two more people to cover up the crime.
Murder? The tisdales?
You better be long and straight on this one, detective.
Harrison's father is terminally ill, sir.
What? I just saw him at a benefit.
Hope you took a picture.
With the sister out of the way, the son will inherit all of it.
Excuse me.
There's also a twisted, emotional angle in there.
I don't wa to bore you with the details.
But family and vengeance--
It's shakespearean.
Harrison just left work.
He's probably headed home to destroy the evidence.
Are you sure you can tie him to the other victims?
Through a patient of his sister's
That he was trying to frame.
It's days like this
I wish i was back in civil division.
Thank you, sir.
Thanks. Soon.
You're home early, mr. Tisdale.
Got a list inside.
Yeah, thanks for your help.
What do we got, guys?
Get this. Junior's business is going under.
He's tens of millions in debt.
But with his sister's share of the tisdale fortune,
He stands to pay off his debt and then some.
Castle, if you're going in, you should be armed.
My backup's in the glove compartment.
I can't find it. It--
This time, you're staying put.
Oh, okay, beckett.
Very funny.
Joke'sver!
Come on!
Cuff me once, shame on you.
Cuff me twice, shame on me.
Harrison tisdale? Nypd. We have a warrant.
Just a minute!
Open the door, harrison!
Open the door. It's nypd. We have a warrant.
He's coming down the fire escape.
He's out back. Cover the front.
Stop! Police! Don't move!
Castle! No!
I got him! I got him!
Castle!
Stay back! Stay back! Don't come anywhere closer!
- Get--Get down! Stay back! Stay back! Don't move!
- Easy, easy!
Let him go, harrison!
- Come on!
- Easy! Easy! Okay. It's okay. Okay.
Castle! Are you okay?
Yeah, except psycho here needs a breath mint.
- Shut up!
- Okay!
Hey, harrison, you know what's bugging me?
If you were that deep in debt,
Why didn't you just ask your father for the money?
Castle! You are not helping!
You know what i think? I think you did ask.
I think you asked, and he said no.
I think he always said no.
Self-Made man like that,
I bet he thought you were weak for asking.
He's the one who was weak!
I was trying to make something with my life,
And all he cared about was her!
That's why you killed her. It wasn't just for the money.
You wanted to punish him before he died,
Take away the only thing he loved.
That's a pretty good story.
Who are you?
Harrison, let him go! It's over.
It's not over, it's not over!
Drop the gun, or i swear to god, i'll--
Tell me you saw that!
You're gonna put that in your report, right?
Can i see the cuffs, please?
Yeah, yeah.
What the hell were you thinking?
You could've gotten yourself killed.
Well, the safety was on the whole time.
You know, you could've told me.
Where's the fun in that?
Well, i guess this is it.
Well, it doesn't have to be.
We could, uh, go to dinner, debrief each other.
Why, castle? Si could be another one of your conquests?
Or i could be one of yours.
It was nice to meet you, castle.
It's too bad.
It would've been great.
You have no idea.
You wanted to see me, sir?
Yeah.
I just got a call from the mayor's office.
Apparently, you have a fan.
A fan, sir?
Rick castle. Seems he's found the main character
For his next set of novels--
A tough but savvy female detective.
I'm flattered?
Don't be. He says he has to do research.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, yes.
- No way.
- Beckett, listen--
Sir, he is like a 9 year old on a sugar rush--
Totally incapable of taking anything seriously.
But he did help solve this case.
And when the mayor's happy, the commissioner's happy.
And when the commissioner's happy, i'm happy.
How long, sir?
=====
welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net