Murder.
Mystery.
The macabre.
What is it about a heart-boiled
detective femme fertile,
and the cold steel of a gun,
keeps our bedside lamps burning
into the wee hours of the morning.
However the spell is cast,
tonight we honor a master of the form
and celebrate the launch
of storm fall.
Call me when you're ready
to wash that off.
The stunning conclusion to his best selling
derek storm mystery series.
Ladies and gentlemen
The master of the macabre,
Rick Castle.
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:FRM@´ó±¦
Sync:FRS@°²ÄÈ¸â
Who are you?
Alison tisdale--
24, grad student at n.Y.U.,
Part of the social work program.
Nice place for a social worker.
Daddy's money.
Neighbors called to complain about the muc.
When she didn't answer,
they had the super check on her.
No signs of struggle.
He knew her.
Even bought her flowers.
Who says romance is dead?
I do, every saturday night.
A little lipstick wouldn't hurt.
I'm just saying.
So what'd he give her besides roses?
Two shots to the chest,
Small caliber.
Does this look familiar to anyone?
No, but i'm not the one with
a thing for freaky ones.
Just give me a "jack shot jill over bill"
So i can get my collar and go home.
Oh, but the freaky ones require more.
They reveal more.
Look at how he left her, covered modestly.
So?
So despite all of the effort,
all of the preparation,
You won't find any evidence of sexual abuse.
You really get that from just this?
This, plus, i've seen this before.
You've seen it before? Where?
Roses on her body, sunflowers on her eyes?
Don't you guys read?
What kind of idiot
Kills off his best-Selling main character?
Are you asking as my bloodsucking publisher
Or as my bloodsucking ex-Wife?
Oh, is that what you're doing?
Punishg me by killing the golden goose?
Oh, come on. I may be petty and shortsighted,
But i'm not that petty and shortsighted.
Really? Then why?
Writing derrick used to be fun.
Now it's like work.
Mm. God forbid you should work.
I mean, you could have retired him,
You could have crippled him.
You could have had him join the friggin' circus.
But, no, you had to put a bullet through his head.
Yeah, real messy, too. Big exit wound.
Don't worry. Derrick storm is not
the golden goose here. I am.
I wrote half a dozen best
sellers before him.
What makes you think i'm gonna stop now?
Oh, i don't know.
The fact the new book was due nine weeks ago?
You can't rush genius.
www.tvsubtitles.net