Save Shelly.
Why, who in the world
let Major Briggs loose, Leo?
lt couldn't have been you, could it?
No, no. No punishment, Leo.
lt's too late for that
to do us any harm.
And l have a new game for you.
Well, here's our contribution
to the Miss Twin Peaks gala buffet.
And l fully expect to see one of you
up there in the winner's circle.
- Dream on, Norma.
- Don't be so sure.
This is the biggest day of the year
for us.
And we have to have somebody
up there
who really deserves this title.
Especially this year.
You mean Laura Palmer?
lt would be a good day for healing.
l think we need more than a day.
So, Norma, are they gonna
honor you tonight
on your 20th anniversary
of winning Miss Twin Peaks?
Don't remind me.
Come on,
if you entered today, you'd win.
Look at you,
you're already working on the judge.
Well, since you mentioned it...
Who are you gonna vote for?
Maybe you could split your vote.
- Hi, Daddy.
- Audrey.
The most intelligent face
that l've seen all day.
You make the rest of us
look like primates.
What's with all the books?
Yes, the Koran,
the Bhagavad-Gita, the Talmud,
the Bible, Old and New Testaments,
the Tao Te Ching.
Audrey, l hold in my hands
those holy books
which constitute
the fundamental framework
of humanity's
philosophy of good.
Somewhere in here
are the answers that l seek.
And l intend to read them
from cover to cover, until l find...
Listen to me prattling on.
lt's Jack, isn't it?
lt's only been a day.
l hope it doesn't hurt this much
in a week.
Honey, may l give you
a piece of ageless wisdom
culled from these volumes?
Time heals all wounds.
l know how it feels.
Believe me.
We barely had time
to know each other.
But the time that you had
was highly concentrated.
lt's the concentrate
they make concentrate from.
l'm afraid l'll never see him again.
Jack is a man of his word.
And if he said that he'd be back,
then he will be back.
l promise you.
Daddy, you can't promise me,
but thanks for wanting to.
l actually came here
to update you on my trip to Seattle.
Right. Update away.
Okay.
The Packards are using
Twin Peaks Savings and Loan
to funnel cash
to the Ghostwood project.
But the bank is keeping
a very low profile.
lt seems they don't want
any bad publicity.
Oh, they don't?
Well, bad publicity
is exactly what they're gonna get.
Audrey, have you given
any more thought
to the Miss Twin Peaks Pageant?
Daddy...
From the bottom of my heart,
l don't wanna be
the town bathing beauty.
l understand.
But Miss Twin Peaks
is the ultimate local forum.
Audrey.
lt would truly be inspirational
to have a winner
with a political sensibility
that extends
beyond makeup strategies
and recipes for cherry pie, huh?
Now, as you know,
each contestant gives a speech
to the assembled town.
This year's theme concerns
our immediate environment.
And what we must do to preserve it.
l know there's another way to do this,
Daddy.
Audrey, make the speech.
Help stop Ghostwood.
And take us to a better day.
Has he taken his eyes off it yet?
Not today.
And before you ask,
we still got people out
combing the woods for Major Briggs.
Harry, considering our mutual
connection to Project Blue Book,
l believe that Windom Earle
has targeted the major.
- What for?
- lnteresting.
l don't know.
But with your permission,
l'd like to speak out loud.
Windom Earle has been
seeking access to the Black Lodge
as far back as 1 965.
This chess game may involve
more pieces
than we've begun to imagine.
Then of course,
there's the mysterious circumstances
surrounding Josie's death
to consider.
What about them?
Consider them how?
When she died-- l'm sorry
l didn't mention this before, Harry,
but l had to take into account
your mental state.
What is it?
She was trembling with fear.
l would go as far as to say
quaking like an animal.
l might venture a guess to say
that it was the fear that killed her.
At the moment of her death...
...l saw Bob.
As if he had slipped in
through some crevice in time.
Upon reflection, l believe
there's a connection
between his appearance
and Josie's fear.
As if he was attracted to it.
Feeding off it somehow.
You see a connection
between Bob and the Black Lodge?
Harry,
l think it's where he comes from.
l think that the Black Lodge
is what you have referred to in the past
as ''the evil in these woods.''
lf Windom Earle is seeking access
to that,
it is imperative that we find our way in
before he does.
There's a source of great power there,
Harry.
Far beyond our ability
to comprehend.
Eureka!
Dale, l could kiss
your pointy little head.
lt's fear.
lt's fear, Leo. That's the key.
My favorite emotional state.
And all this time,
it's been staring me right in the kisser.
Leo, it's marvelous, a perfect fit.
These night creatures that hover
on the edge of our nightmares
are drawn to us
when we radiate fear.
lt's their bread and butter.
A perfect symbiosis.
Oh, nature,
perfect in design and aspects.
You do not disappoint!
Leo, look lively.
Victory is at hand.
We know where the entrance is.
We know when the lock appears.
Now we hold the key in our hands.
Forgive my hasty departure,
dear one.
The time has come
to gather my beloved queen
and embark
upon our dark honeymoon.
l haven't been this excited
since l punctured Caroline's aorta.
Leo, we must share
a final sentiment.
During our time together
in this verdant bower,
l must confess, l've developed
something of a fondness for you.
Sounding board, companion,
ever obedient and faithful.
An overall A for effort, Leo.
But l'm still a trifle miffed
at your release of Major Briggs.
But then, you'll have plenty of time
to reflect upon that, won't you?
Goodbye, Leo.
And good luck.
One and two and three, step four.
And one and two--
Let the mood carry you.
Don't be afraid of your vulnerability.
Show me more leg.
What kind of a dance
is this supposed to be, Mr. Pinkle?
lt's a dance of nature, my friend.
lt's a celebration.
All right, girls.
Now, turn around
and bend forward
like a sapling.
A sapling in the wind.
That's it. A little bit more, and hold it.
What exactly are we celebrating
with us all bending over like this?
Don't ever question the vision
of your choreographer!
You are but a petal on my rose.
Now, please, people.
On the count of one.
One and two and three and four.
And one and two
- and three and four...
- l love a chorus line.
lf we could just focus here
for a second.
l've gotta get back to the diner.
Now, what qualities do we think
best exemplify Miss Twin Peaks?
Beauty and power.
That's the way l like them.
Poise and, God help us,
a sophistication
and breeding.
Well, l think a major factor
should be originality.
Well, wouldn't that fall under talent?
lt's always nice when it does.
Personally,
l've always been big on style.
l think this is enough
for me to work with,
so l'm gonna go back
and work up the scoresheets,
and l'll see you tonight.
- Terrific.
- Bye.
And three and four.
Okay, that's a break, team.
Hi, Dick. We're on break.
Hi, Lana.
Would you mind helping me
find something in the storage room?
Storage room?
We're missing
a very important prop.